Which is better, AML or WebDev for secure future and more earning.
The first thing is that no one knows about future.
AML is still a little bit early.
We are going through a lot of things.
We have already booked a ticket.
We are going through a lot of blockchains.
So these are trends that we are going through.
So you have to learn from one day.
The main thing is, the concept is the basic clear.
The base is your strongness.
The C++ Python is the strongest.
When you are trying to catch a trend,
But you are starting to learn AML now.
Because now, the 24th is still the same.
The 23th is not the 23th.
The 23th is still a little bit early.
Because, the things are coming out.
The models are getting designed.
Everything is growing.
So this will be the trend.
So, take care of this.
After that, keep the base strong.
If you want to jump into something in the future,
Then you can do it.
Now, you can do AML inside Python.